♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ and they shot him into space ♪
♪ Get me down ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can
find, la la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor
his mind, la la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end, la la la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot, show yourself ♪
♪ Gypsy, I'm not ready ♪
♪ Tom Servo, hello there ♪
♪ Crow, that's one O ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science
facts, la la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself,
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(doors closing)
- Well, hi there, howdy do.
- Hi.
(robot laughing)
- Mike Nelson here with
my friends Tom Servo
and Crow T. Robot.
And today we're glad
you stopped by today
because we've got
a special treat,
Lisa Lobe!
- Lisa Lobe?
- Is gonna stop
by and do a song.
♪ You say I only hear
what I wanna hear ♪
♪ And I say did you get
my note in study hall ♪
♪ I asked you if you liked me ♪
♪ And if you'd like
me like I like you ♪
♪ Then check the box
saying that you like me ♪
♪ Yeah you really like me ♪
♪ Turn the TV on ♪
♪ Turn the TV off ♪
♪ Its my turn to watch
what I wanna watch ♪
♪ And throw me the remote ♪
♪ And turn the TV on ♪
♪ Turn the TV on ♪
♪ 'cause there's
a singer singing ♪
♪ Bout how she likes a guy ♪
♪ And she wonders does
the guy like her too ♪
♪ But he doesn't ♪
♪ She made it up in her head ♪
♪ He doesn't like her ♪
♪ You say you're gonna
ask her to the prom ♪
I don't know, the kids
seem to like Lisa Lobe.
- Lisa Lobe?
I thought she was Courtney Hole.
- No, Courtney Hole is with
- A lemon holes
- Her hole.
- No.
- We'll be right back.
- Garnishing pumpkin.
- Pumpkin holes.
♪ Glad you missed me, ♪
♪ Yeah you missed ♪
- Come on, come.
- Let me up.
- Come on.
Oh we hurt your feelings?
Good!
- Oh come on Crow I
mean she's all right.
I mean so she's really
annoying we'll just stop that,
oh the bads are calling.
- Oh there they are.
What?
(man hitting keyboard)
- Have, have you been helped?
- No as a matter of
fact, we haven't.
- Well, what are you,
Frank, could you just step
back just a bit please.
Frank, who are these people,
how did they get in here?
- I don't know, have
you been helped?
- No in fact we haven't.
- Frank we have got to start
using the security system!
Mike, have you had any problems
with security up there?
- No, no, everything's--
- What about Lise Hole?
- Oh oh yeah right, Lisa
Lobe stopped by earlier but,
- Oh, you see what I mean Frank?
We've got these
idiots down here,
they got Lisa Lobe
running around, oh, sorry.
- Have you been helped?
- Frank!
No I'm gonna go outside
to check this out.
And when I tell you,
hold this button down
and buzz me in, all right?
- [Man On Speaker] All right
Frank, it's me, buzz me in.
- Hi welcome to Bargain Clown,
can I take your order please?
- [Man On Speaker] Very funny
Frank, would you buzz me in?
- I'm sorry, that's
not on the menu sir!
- [Man On Speaker] Frank
I will kill you so bad.
- Uh that's $4.99 please!
(group laughing)
(man hitting ground)
- Shut up!
Well Mike, because of our
little security problem,
we're going to
have to communicate
via closed circuit intercom.
Check, check,
okay Mike, is this thing on?
Can you hear me?
- No I'm sorry Dr.
F we can't hear you.
- [Dr. F] Oh what the heck,
I must have crossed those
wires coming out of the...
How about now?
- Uh, nope, still
nothing on this end.
- [Dr. F] Well son of a...
Do you happen to have channel A?
- Which channel would you
like us to have it on?
- [Dr. F] Channel A.
- Uh, we have it on channel
A, we just can't hear you.
- Well all right all right,
turn it off, turn it off.
I'll just have to
describe your movie
using semifour flags.
I've got a treat
coming up for you.
It's a short subject called.
Are you ready for marriage?
Hope you enjoy and good sailing!
- Okay then, thanks a lot hey,
and sorry this
thing didn't work.
- Hey!
- Oh, we have moving sides!
- [Dr. F] Face!
(futuristic bops)
- Ha ha ha face.
- Total face.
- Um, yeah I'm
sick of sex anyway.
- Yes it's my long-time
bachelor Reuben Hill.
I have to wear this dress, it's
part of my family research.
- All stress.
- Oh, Professor Hill, sir.
- Say, nice front porch.
- Um, mom, I need
to get to school.
- The tepid embrace tells me
they're ready for marriage.
- Welcome to as far
as you're gonna get.
- Oh you're so suitable.
♪ Happy trails to you ♪
- Goodnight sweetheart.
- Goodnight darling.
- I touched your vitalis,
I'm gonna go wash my hands.
- Larry, isn't exciting
about our getting married.
- What, yeah, what!
Yeah, what?
Oh, oh, oh, could you
grab me a cold shower
while you're in there?
Thank you.
- Uh, you still didn't
pay your grid bill ma'am.
- I hope Leopold doesn't
find out about this.
- Um, I'm pretty sure this
is my house but, you know...
- Walking on a pink cloud.
So I asked her last night
at a graduation prom
and she said yes.
We're going to be
married, in August!
- Wow, married?
- Sly.
- She's just
finishing high school
and you still have two
years of University.
- And what about me?
- That's a tough road Larry.
What are you going
to use for money?
- Well, Sue's folks
were gonna pay something
to put her in junior college
here in town for two years,
so we'll have that.
But instead of going to college
she'll get a full-time
job in Campustown.
- It's just Campustown Jake.
- Says she doesn't care
anymore about education.
So with that, and my part
time job, we'll get by.
- We'll be selling plasma!
Uh oh, here's Sue now.
You two probably
want to me alone.
- Oh why are you still
wearing a headdress?
- Why Sue honey.
- Oh Larry.
- Well what's the matter?
- It's the folks they,
we had a terrible scene.
- I got kicked out of L7.
- I couldn't keep a wink.
They don't approve,
they say I'm too young!
They want me to finish two
more years of schooling
before I even get engaged.
Oh Larry.
- Oh Rob.
- Buck up sweetheart,
they can't stop me!
- I'm mighty boy.
- Relax,
and act normal 'till after
your graduation next week.
- I'll contact the underground.
- And I can borrow Phil's car,
we'll go down to Greeneville,
there's a Justice of
the Peace down there.
- I'll marry him.
- We'll elope honey!
- But married, I
wanted a church wedding
and all the parties and
showers for me too and--
- And the annulment.
- My folks, that would
break mom's heart.
- Well we're the ones
that are getting married,
not your folks.
- I hate you.
- I don't know Larry.
- I'm really mousey.
- I read somewhere
that a marriage without
parents approval
has two strikes on
it from the start.
- I think it was from
humor and uniform.
- But if eloping
is the only way.
- No.
Maybe it isn't.
- I could have my
chin smallered.
- Maybe you could
convince your folks
that you should get married.
- But how Larry, how?
- Tell them we're Pixies.
- I'm sitting in a puddle.
- I bet we could get some advice
from the marriage counselor
over at the church.
His name is Hall.
- Hunce Hall?
- Phil told me about him.
He teaches a course on
marriage and family living
at the college.
- You think he could
help me with my folks?
- No.
- It's worth a try, isn't it?
- Visit your government church.
- First federal
church, member of FDIC.
- My folks don't
understand the way I feel.
- They feel like rhino hide.
- But that's the story Mr. Hall.
- Do you think you can
help us get married?
- Pair Oburst!
- Why I'm in favor of marriage.
In fact, I spent a
good deal of my time
helping people to get
ready for marriage.
- And I'm in the
concrete business.
- Now let's see, you've
know each other for,
- Three months, one week
two days and, 17 hours.
- Oh boy, one of these.
- And you're 18 Sue?
- Si.
- And 19 Larry?
- Thank you.
- [Hall] Have either of you
ever been in love before?
- Well,
- Does my uncle count?
- But not like this,
this is the real thing.
- Yes.
- Ha ha, no it isn't.
- I had a chum in college
who had the real thing
with eight successive girls.
- Wilt Chamberlain?
- Boy it's all right
if you have it, fine,
it's a very important factor
in building a happy marriage.
- I found that out to late but--
- How do you know
it's real love?
The kind you can get married on?
- Why, ever since
I first met Larry
I haven't wanted to
date anyone else.
- Except Dwight Eisenhower.
- A whole three months now.
And besides I haven't even
had one quarrel with him.
- In the car Sue!
- No quarrels, why not?
No differences of opinion,
or no opinion?
- Objection, he's
leading the witness.
- What do you talk
about on your dates?
- Oh, movies and popular songs.
- Orchestras and dancing.
- Popular songs.
- [Hall] Larry, chosen
profession, engineering?
- No I don't
understand any of it.
- It's gross.
- I don't like to hear about it.
- Sue honey, I didn't
know you felt that way.
- That's because
you never listen!
- Larry you're a dollard.
- Well it seems you two
may have some things
to talk over and settle.
- Idiots.
- Might well ask
yourself some questions
before you get too
serious about marriage..
- Well what do you mean?
- What sort of questions?
- Well, questions for cupid.
Might say he should ask them
before he fires those arrows.
- Are you licensed sir?
- We call this
Cupid's checklist.
- And we have entered
your fantasy kingdom.
- Do you have similar
backgrounds, similar bases
for your ideals and standards?
- Pure bloodlines.
- Second,
- Cupid is anal..
- Second, are you real
friends, comrades, pals,
through thick and thin.
- Third--
- Are you from the same family?
- You both understand marriage.
- Huh?
- Well, not the kind
in most movies or
most popular songs.
- We love popular songs.
- But the real everyday
kind of marriage
between real people,
do you understand?
- Well golly Mr. Hall I
don't know the answers
to all those questions,
I just know that I'm in
love with Sue, is that bad?
- No that's good.
- Shut up Iris.
- You're right, and it's
good when you recognized
that you don't know what the
answer is, it's a good sign.
- I don't know.
- Anything!
- I think we're friends.
And maybe we can
understand marriage but,
backgrounds, how do they
affect getting married?
- Well, come over here a minute.
Perhaps I can show
you what I mean.
- Put these on.
- What's that?
- I call it a marriage
development board.
- Pat and pending.
- It represents the
psychological distance
between a husband and a wife
from the time they are
born until they die.
- Bobby Orr's electric
marriage, real marriage action.
- What does it all mean?
- Well let's set it
up for you and Sue.
When you are born, you inherit
(robots giggling)
a great many differences
from your parents.
That's part of your background.
- That makes sense all right.
- Now, as you grow up,
you each develop separate
and unique personalities.
- Unless your Finnish.
- Your mental growth--
- Represented by Tom Duey.
- Your emotional hub.
- It's a little Hitler baby.
- Your standards and ideals.
- Your Zephon Wars
from Beta Three.
- Larry your distinctly
masculine outlook on life.
- Thank you.
- Sue your feminine way
of looking at things.
- Is wrong.
- Your capacities
to love, be loved.
- Are all missing.
- These and many other ways,
you each require a background
so when you first met, you
were probably farther apart.
Probably more
distinct individuals
then when you were born.
- But I don't want to
marry a girl like me.
I want to marry a man like him.
- Ha ha ha no you don't.
- But even though we're
close together here,
we don't know how far
apart we are there.
- That's right.
- When you two met,
there was probably
an early physical reaction.
- Oh yeah.
- A romantic attraction
that pulls you together.
A love appeal that
hits you sort of,
boing,
- You saw my boing?
- [Larry] How did you know?
- Well it happened to me.
It happened to some
degree to most couples
who become happily married
but it takes more
than this boing.
- Sometimes there's a schplurt!
- You're too far
apart psychologically.
- If one of you is cuckoo.
- If you're backgrounds
are not similar enough.
It can cause a great deal
of argument and unhappiness
until--
(rubber band snapping)
- It's gone.
- Where'd it go?
- We're gonna die!
- That's what you'll be saying
about your romantic love
if these other things
cause a break up.
- But where's the rubber band!
- This is forever
with Larry and me.
- Fine, I hope so.
(funky '80s music)
But, don't you think
it's wise to take time
to find out how much
strain these differences
might put on your romantic love.
- But there isn't any time.
Larry's going away in
a couple of months.
- I am?
- Yes.
Did you two ever see figures
on length of engagement
and how it relates
to your chances
for happiness in marriage.
- It's too technical sir.
- Two separate studies show
the chance for happiness
improves with a
longer engagement.
- You color good sir.
- It's fair for six
months, better for a year,
or two years.
- And so on into infinity.
- Is that because
there's a better chance
to find out some of
these differences
and become real friends?
- Yes, the chance to find
out if your relationship
will wear well.
- Yes but can't we
settle these differences
after we're married?
- Honey this is man talk.
- And if you aren't successful?
- We'll there's
drinking and porno.
- Before you become
too deeply involved,
find out of the distance might
turn out to be too great.
- I've asked King
Vitaman to join us.
- Here's another angle that
should interest you both.
How age when married can effect
the chance for happiness.
- Can I see the raw data?
- You can see that
the chances are better
after the man reaches 21 or so.
- Remember I made this all up.
Here we have the frequency
response of the JBL.
- And the same studies
show that the woman
must be 19 or 20 before
the chances for happiness
begin to be good.
- But why?
What's the difference
between 19 and 21 or so.
- Don't sass me son.
- The difference is
you the next few years.
You Larry, and you Sue.
And young people seem to change
and mature in these years
from 18 to 21 and even later.
- I'm not mature?
- The person you might
marry at 18 or so,
will seem like quite a
difference person to you
a few years later.
- Is that like Transformers?
- Gee hun.
- Guess I don't like you.
- Doesn't take an
engineer to see--
- I'm not listening.
Dum dum dum dum, not listening!
Dum-de dum dum dum.
- All of them.
- Yeah.
- Gee Bullwinkle.
- I see our chances
aren't so good now.
What are we going to do?
I thought you were going
to help us get married.
- Well frankly neither of you
has a chance for love ever.
- So, you're available soon?
- I believe I can.
I think you two have
a lot of what it takes
to build a successful marriage.
Yet, you wouldn't try to plan
and build a house in
three months will you?
- Sure why not?
- Shouldn't a marriage
have better planning?
- On belay!
- If you two are going to
build a successful family team
that will last for
40 or 50 years,
- Suddenly their marriage
is the Igersanction.
- How long do you think it
should take to get ready?
- It's approaches
engineering, look out!
- All right.
- You wanna play rough?
- How do we know
when we've done it?
- Oh boy, back to the dolls!
- When the two of you
are ready for marriage,
you sense a new
feeling between you.
The two of you united as a pair.
Thinking as one unit,
acting as one unit
in the building of a
marriage and a new family.
- Form all commando units.
- Your essential parents
shows up in the way
in which you consider
what's best for the
pair of you, or,
what you want
individually for yourself.
Think of how often
you speak of things
from my point of view.
- Oh I know.
(robots shushing)
Marines, we are leaving!
- Sorry back in Danang
there for a minute.
- I guess it wasn't my folks
that needed convincing,
it's me, I mean it's
us, isn't it Larry?
- Yeah, we'll say.
(robots snickering)
- And so in terms of
the checklist for Cupid,
Larry and Sue began to examine
their readiness for marriage.
- They were horrified
by what they found.
- [Sue] Do we have
similar backgrounds?
- Do we have any pryers?
- [Sue] Do we agree on
our religious beliefs?
- I worship Cthulhu.
- And have the same feelings
about religion in general.
- You know, God and stuff.
- Do we have the same
ideals and standards
and pace?
So give to me your leather
take from me my lace.
It's the Hitlers!
- Do we enjoy the same friends?
- Hi we're running for congress.
- Do we share the
same interests?
I like stuff too.
And what about Sue and Me?
- She's suing him?
- Are we real friends?
- I never had a friend.
- Do we have a real
happiness in being together,
talking.
- Boinging.
- Or just doing
nothing together?
- To the point that
we're sick of each other.
- Does each of us really want
to make the other one happy?
- Well I can tell mayonnaise
from salad dressing.
- No you cannot.
- It's easy, come on,
just get, get some...
- Do we have a real
interest in each other
and a sense of
pride in each other?
- Hi Roy, who's the beard?
Oh oh, sorry.
I decided not to jump.
- Do we know each
other's peculiarities?
- I like to sleep with my
head in a catchers mitt.
- Do we both have the
spirit of give and taken?
- Well my lips are all numb.
- Can we quarrel and,
and come out of it with
something better than before.
- Your breath is really bad.
Know what I mean,
it's really pungent.
- Oh.
- Do we really
understand marriage?
- That's the breaded thing
with the mayonnaise right?
Do we understand the
social aspects of marriage?
- I'm not doing that.
- Could we in understanding
about money matters
and how important it is
to have enough money to
do more than just get by.
- Here's a good one son.
- Do we understand
the physical aspect
and the family side of marriage.
- Yes dad that is a doggy, good.
- Do we know how much work
there is to a marriage.
- Yeah got anymore
of these books son?
- And overall, do we have
a feeling of paired unity.
- Hair unity?
- Those questions were
helping us to find out
just how strong our
relationship was.
And helping us to strengthen it.
- Let's get out of
here I need you now.
So the next time we
called on Mr. Hall,
we realized how much
he had been helping us.
He had been talking for
some time with our parents
and there seemed to be general
agreement that Sue and I.
- Should be kept far apart.
- Now have a much better idea
of just how much psychological
distance still separated us.
- If you want to Sue,
your mother and I, we
can make arrangements
for you to begin school at
State U this fall with Larry.
To stay with the junior college.
- With a new car!
- If we want to,
- And if you two get
along, in school that is,
- I made a little funny there.
- If you continue to reduce
the psychological distance,
then perhaps at Christmas
vacation or at Easter vacation,
we'll be glad to
announce the engagement.
- Oh Larry!
- College is gonna
change everything!
- And then we can be married
when Larry graduates
in two years.
I mean, one year and,
ten months and,
three days.
- God that bugs me
when you do that!
- Yes.
If the engagement period
gives you two the opportunity
to work things out together.
- Ill be shocked.
- If you both still want it.
- I guess you might say,
we're engaged to be engaged.
- What are you doing, stop
that, get your hand off me!
- Mr. Hall, I.
- I love you.
- We both want to thank you.
(robots grunting)
Now do you think we have
anything more than--
- Boing?
- Why yes I think
you've made a good start towards
getting ready for marriage.
- But never make
light of boings son.
- Boing everybody!
- Boings all around.
(doors slamming shut)
- Oh ah, ah Mike!
I would like to ask you for
Servos' hand in marriage.
- Sure, I don't see why not.
No, what?
Did I hear you right,
you wanna marry--
- Tom Servo.
- Wuh, why?
- Well I'm not
getting any younger.
- Did he say yes?
Please tell me he
said yes, please say
that we can be joined together
and ride on a magic carpet
to a land of
whimsical enchantment.
Do we have our answer?
- He didn't say.
- What a boner man, geez.
- You guys, getting
married isn't about
just settling for
who's ever there,
there's the whole
question of compatibility.
You know as a matter of fact
there's a compatibility
quiz in this month's Cosmo,
why don't we start there?
- A quiz in Cosmo?
How unusual.
- All right, here it is, okay.
Which, who do you admire
more as a father figure,
Bill Cosby or Marvin Gaye Sr.?
- Bill Cosby.
- Marvin Gaye Sr.
Okay admittedly he
was a little strict.
- In matters of the heart,
which of the three stooges do
you base your decisions on?
- Joe Boeser.
- Curly Joe Dorito.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- That's weird man,
God, that is strange.
- Okay last one, this
one is kind of important,
do you want to get married.
- No.
- Well okay, I add 'em up there,
I guess that last one
puts you over the edge.
Helen Curly Brown
gives you her blessing.
- All right all right all right.
- Mmmmmmm.
(kissing sounds)
- No no no, don't you
don't you, get away, get!
- Ha ha, I kissed him.
- Dreamy, come here you.
- Marriage, hah!
What would you know
about marriage.
- Well I know that if a
marriage is stretched too much,
it can snap!
- It's gone, where did it go!
- Be careful! I gotta send
you your feature presentation,
racket girls.
- Well I know that if the
movie is too long it can snap!
- Where did it go?
- He's a sorcerer!
(funky '80s music)
(robots giggling)
- Woo.
- Whoa, a screen classics,
we'll decide if it's a
screen classics, all right?
- Boy that music draws you in.
- Oh!
I guess it's any given
day at Madonna's house.
- Wow, what if you saw
your grandma in the ring?
- Sir, please get
back to your seat sir.
- This is amazing, can
you just keep doing this?
- Folks we'll be starting
our movie in a minute
but first enjoy this.
- Is there a midway nearby?
Two dominant male women
fight for supremacy.
- Boy these Eastern European
lingerie shows, I tell ya.
- Boing, boing,
- Amanda Pearson, Sandra
Burnhardt go at it.
- Dis, mountain!
Girls, you're both pretty!
- Uh Susan, you could have
at least shaved you legs.
- Uh, Elvis throws
another party.
Bob Crane's private
video collection.
Ah, they're wrestlers!
- Ah, that's Clara's
wrestling name.
Her real name is Savage Venus.
Apples, peaches, pages pie.
By the way the referee
is Charlie Watts,
in case you're wondering.
- Oh dear I just
need to ask you,
where are the keys
to the other...
- She's doing a fish flop again.
- I'd say the DRA fundraiser
is going quite well!
- Mike is this the
thrilla from Manila?
- Uh, no it's the
Snooze in Santa Cruz.
- And four hours later,
- Boy continental sound
really came through.
No wonder people went
nuts over The Beatles,
this is all there was!
♪ Dance with me ♪
♪ I want to be your
partner can't you see ♪
♪ Do do do do ♪
- We salute you George Weiss
for the courage to put
your fantasies on screen.
- Fanta-screen.
- You know Derteno is an
effective denta-frist.
- Come on, get some jello
or mud or oil or something.
- Honey, which can't you
just to go bridge club
or have coffee with
the neighbor ladies?
I demand that recipe Sherry!
- The audience is expecting
a Jim Fowler travel log.
(robots whooing)
(robots knawing)
- Wayne Newton!
Yo 11,
danke shen, right, thank you.
- There's some guys so ugly
they have to become thugs.
Plays of the Week!
You supposed they're
all on the same cycle?
- Uh, could you, move your leg,
just a little, move the leg.
Uh uh, oh, wait.
- Here I'll get it.
Boy this thing is
really stuck, ow, oh!
- Mother start fighting!
- I knew if baseball
went on strike,
other sports would take over.
- Tonight, we dance.
♪ Duh duh duh duh duh duh ♪
♪ Bop bop bop bop
bop bop bop bop ♪
- Wait a minute, is this
gonna be about wrestling?
- So they have 40 minute
rounds in women's wrestling.
Mary McCarthy and Lillian
Helmond have it out.
♪ Sisters sisters ♪
♪ Never were there
such devoted sisters ♪
Hard to remember when this was
a Saturday morning tradition.
- Those ringside seats are
worth the $700 aren't they?
- Remember when Bobby Riggs
wrestled Billy Jeane King?
- Oh yeah.
Well, this is the singing
nun in their declining years.
- Here, does that feel good,
I'll just lay it
gently against that.
- No.
- Ah, ah.
Peloma Polkowska's enjoying it.
- You want ju ju bees
or jersey for me?
- Uh, ju ju bee's fine.
- You want ju ju fruit?
- No ju ju beans.
- Ju ju beans or ju ju fruit?
- Ju ju beans.
- I'll get 'em.
He had his hat in
his lap for a reason.
- Linda, do you just wanna knock
off and go get some coffee?
- I saw this match on Lifetime.
- Hey it's Harpo!
(robot whooping)
- I prefer the
traditional Hamlet.
♪ She holds the title
and never lets go ♪
♪ That is why the
lady is a champ ♪
- Hey it's Fran Liebowitz!
Not writing...
- Of course.
Well they're trying to
spice up this production
of St. Jone and it's
just not working.
- Well this is just the pro am,
there's four rounds
over the weekend.
Sometimes it's
hard to be a woman!
I'll pin it on my sweater!
- Scene is cut from
the turning point.
- Thank you thank you,
come and see me in Hell Italian,
damn the question.
- I had $20 bucks on you!
- Geez her breasts
are on her shoulders.
- Don't talk about
her son mother.
- Not yet, later, later, please.
- Ah the fun marriage
of Sharon Doeherty
and Ashley Hamilton.
- Are they getting turned on?
Timothy Busfield.
Hey look it's Timothy Busfield,
yeah it is, it's
Timothy Busfield.
Okay, ju ju bee's it
is, come on let's go.
- Yeah men always have to
go the bathroom in pairs.
- Oh boy those guys are
slippery, they almost got away.
- Tenth time I said no,
you stay right here.
- You cannot wrestle
in satin tap pants.
- Misses Oh-hooeygins.
- The girls show up yet?
- Quit worrying, she's
waiting right outside.
- Well send her in.
Peaches, you know we signed
up the arena the other night?
- Oh yeah.
- Peaches, mhm.
- Welcome Peaches, can
I call you Peaches?
- You sure can Mr. Gally.
- This is Joe.
- How do you do Joe?
- How do you do?
- Peaches and Regalia.
- Peach is your real name?
- Oh yes!
- Is 4'9" your real height?
- I can see I don't
have to be reminded.
- Shut up Joe.
- Why don't you sit down?
- Thank you.
- Her next guest Dagmar
ladies and gentleman.
- I was certainly happy
I was able to purchase
your contract from Herman,
now that you have no
objections to the deal.
- Nice hand.
- Why should I?
I hope to be a champ,
with your help.
- I'll do all I can,
I promise you then.
- You're very kind Mr. Scalli.
- We'll do all we can
to make you happy.
You'll see that all your
needs are taken care of.
- All he can.
- Thank you Mr. Scalli.
- I'm very grateful for you
kindness and help Mr. Scalli.
- And now let me tell
you about plans for you.
- Ah!
Whoa is this me in my head
trying to cope with this movie
or is this actually
happening on the screen?
- No I'm I'm, I'm seeing it too.
- Oh me too, this would
turn Katie Langheader on.
Sorry, little fantasy there.
- I think it's a wonderful idea.
- No that we've become
friends, why don't you drop
the Mr. Scalli,
just call me Scalli.
- Felonuis Hebadies Scalli.
- Fine Scalli.
- Hey and don't
forget me, I'm Joe!
- Oh Joe, you're cute.
- I get it, anything
that is small is cute!
Well, that's me!
- He's from Barcelona.
- Don't you know the best
things come in small packages.
- Not my way of thinking.
- I always am fast
sized, the wrong word.
- And how about
showing you the gym.
You're gonna be spending most
of your time there anyways.
- It's a good idea.
- Peaches, you're the good idea.
(funky '80s music)
Never saw my grandma naked
but this will do.
- Shh, people are wrestling!
- This is back when
undergarments had
no erotic appeal.
- Ruby, I want you
to meet Miss Page.
- How do you do?
- Hello.
- Visiting our gym?
- No I purchased Peach,
Miss Page's contract.
She's now a member of our gym.
- Well I'm delighted
to hear that.
- You have a nice place here.
- Oh we're all just members
of one big happy family.
So the saying goes.
- I have a suggestion Miss Page,
why don't you
change to gym tards
and spend a few minutes getting
acquainted with our gym?
- But Mr. Scalli I have
no gym tards with me.
- I'm sure Ruby can help.
- Why yes,
I'm sure we can borrow something
out of the locker room,
I'll be glad to help.
- Why don't you Peaches?
I mean Miss Page.
- Okay if you say so Scalli.
- Follow me Peaches.
- Are you a good
witch of a bad witch?
- It's that guy's seventh year
in an unpaid internship.
- Hey Joe.
- Where you going with
that gun in your hand?
- Oh lubricious Mediterranean
guys, they're always so cute.
- Where you going?
- Force of habit boss.
- Well change your habit.
Come on I want to talk
to you in the office.
- Nahhh.
- Let me see,
yes we can use these
trunks and this bra
and you're all set.
- Bra?
- If I'd know that they
wanted me to work out
in the man I would have
brought my own gym tards along.
- Oh don't worry, somebody's old
something around
this dressing room
and it won't hurt to borrow it.
- I believe this
is not gratuitous.
- Here's my bungy cord.
Give me that leg.
- That's it you're all set,
now we can go to the gym.
- Meanwhile Audrey Hepburn
was making "Roman Holiday."
New girls got an odd can.
- Did you notice that new
girl Scalli dragged in?
- Yeah I heard he just
picked up her contract.
- Oh Jethro!
- She's up to something
no good if you ask me.
- Bet you he gave her
the same line he gave me
when I first came here.
- Yeah he's full
of big promises.
- Kind of like looking at
an erotic cave painting.
Ooh she moves fast
for a lineman.
- Don't tell me you
fell for his lie.
- Well, didn't you.
- What's that gunk on her towel?
- Yes, I guess that makes
us birds of a feather.
Well come on, let's
go to the showers.
- So the shower is a
formal high helic Asian.
- Oh yeah yeah.
- Those of you who never
associated sexuality
with your great
aunt, here it is.
My mats are so dingy.
- Oh that one was personal.
- You know Peach's bikini
sold at Softy's for $50,000?
Just trying to get
a workout here,
just trying to get my heart
rate up a little, thank you.
- I can see that no one
asked too many questions
about Peaches.
- Joe is shrinking.
- Word will get
around fast enough
when they find out I
bought her contract.
- Don't worry boss, I
know how to play dumb.
- Now that you don't
have to tell me.
What I want you to do is
shadow her at all times
but don't let her know about it.
- Leave it to me boss.
I used to work for
Frednose Flynn, remember?
- I didn't ask for references,
just follow my instructions.
- Okay boss.
- I'm practically putting
her in your charge.
She's our new star wrestler.
- Leave everything to me boss.
This is one job I
won't fall down on.
- You better not.
- Baravelli.
- Now I'll phone and
see that she moves
into our same apartment house.
- See how I'm calling here?
You can watch it if you want.
- He's got a Hal Linden look.
- Hello Johnson?
Scalli.
Listen I want you to
do me a little favor.
- Here's a clean towel.
You can use it to
dry yourself with
after you've had your
shower in the next room.
- Thanks, thanks a lot.
- Oh, I'm going over
to Mr. Scalli's office,
but I'll be back
in a few minutes.
- Put in a good
word for me, huh?
- I don't think I'll have to.
- How does the towel work?
- Wuh?
- Ah.
I love the rings, woopee!
- Well, she has the
build and the strength.
Something like a
fifth avenue bus.
- I bought her contract.
She'll bring a lot of
extra business for the gym.
How about taking her out
for some road work tomorrow?
- Well that's an excellent
idea, I'll go back and tell her.
- I'll have her
fill some potholes!
You know when Ed Wood saw this
it was like when Trufoe
saw Citizen Kane.
(birds whistling)
Oh, it's so hot out today.
Prelude to the afternoon
for a hot fawn.
- This is in danger of being
confiscated while we watch it.
- It could be,
now that bra's about as sexy
as a concrete a button it.
- You're really good at
that, you're so smart.
- Well, Heidi's all frown up!
- Okay, Shmele's
gonna hit you hot,
think body body!
- Child avern.
- Chow Shirley.
- One two 12, 25,
eleventy-two, 63, 98, 12,
four,
- Well where's Benny Hill
when you need him huh?
- Hey, you look like
a swell dish to me.
- Chaplin speaks!
Murlese Brom is playing
on the car radio.
(car engine running)
Hey, why don't we
do it in the road?
No one will be watching us.
- And the point of this is...
'Cause it's the annual
running of the breasts.
- Ah, just breathe the
fumes in, it's good for ya.
- This movie is
refreshingly itself.
- Usually when I run with
a big breath of jogger,
I'm shy and awkward.
- Posture Scalli.
Late last night or night before,
24 rappers came
knocking at my door.
And, uh, uh.
- Sure hope she's
not in a fault line.
- Wow!
- Duh duh sss!
- So when Joe went into
the employment agency,
did he say I like driving
women wrestlers to the country
and looking at their breasts.
- I'm getting a
really good workout.
- So is Joe.
- Boss.
- There were three men that
were looking for you yesterday
are here.
- Where?
- They're in your office.
- And so student, just plug
in the quadratic formula
and excuse us.
- Hey you catch the
live Riley last night?
Pretty good.
Hi we're here to
do greater tuna.
- We've been waiting
to see you Scalli.
- So I had a stand.
- Radio free up!
- I figured you'd be
showing up anyway.
- You guessed it right,
what's on your chest?
- Just a rash.
- Mr. Big's got an idea.
You've been bucking
a lot of dough.
- Yeah you're short
on kicking in.
- I've bucketed nothing, you've
got the wrong information.
- It isn't what we heard,
you might as well level.
- We've got a way of
finding things out Steve.
Your boy Jimmy ratted.
- Jimmy ratted?
Why that--
- Jimmy is working
for Mr. Big now.
- Nah.
- Sort of personal,
you can't touch him.
- Okay.
- Good Fred bigger willing pig.
- Who would you figure
he's got coming?
- You got a nail clipper?
- $35,000 grand,
and he wants it now.
Mr. Big ain't a
patient man Scalli.
- I haven't got
that much right now.
Painted my rug.
- Yeah, my heart
bleeds for you Scalli.
When?
- Give me 30 days or so.
- Is he kiddin'?
We gotta have some security.
- Nevermind, it's a lot of time.
I'll speak to Mr. Big and
see how he feels about it.
- He's the big from
Big and Tall fame.
- Kinda nice to be
alive, isn't it Scalli.
- Is it the boss?
- Yeah.
- We'll be seeing you.
- You know all the old
familiar, well you know.
- Let's go back to Rockville!
(Scalli slamming desk)
- Should have put
up chips and dip.
- It's this punk, Scalli's
confidential bookkeeper.
- Well, well.
- He's kinda cooked up.
- I've been looking
forward to meeting you.
Come closer I wanna
take a good look at you.
- I just got contacts.
- Yeah you look
smug, just right.
- He's one of the undead boss.
- Lucky I've known luck for
a long time, he's okay chief.
He and I did time
together up the river.
- Good enough.
- Can you wake him up?
- Well Monk, you're
in my pay now,
but you still work
for Scalli too.
- Glad to be of service.
- He looks like a bush baby.
- Just keep an eye on Scalli.
I want you to report to
me every move he makes,
especially the amount
of money he buckets.
He does it regularly doesn't he?
- Well I'm his
confidential bookkeeper.
- Hoo hoo!
- Don't be afraid,
speak up, you're
amongst friends.
- Yes.
- Whoa ho ho ho!
- He does bucket
bets, almost daily.
He keeps the money
in his office safe.
- That's enough.
We'll just nurse Scalli
along for the present.
Just keep your mouth
good and tight.
- Don't worry about me
boss, I know my business.
- Okay, Connie will
show you the way out.
- Boy I can't believe
how small Mr. Big is.
(funky '80s music)
- Yeah.
(Mike and Crow coughing)
- It's--
- Fun, fun.
- Well what do you say buddy,
I think it's abut time
for the, entertainment?
- Entertainment.
- Well yeah what's a swinging
Bachelor party without,
entertainment, hit it boys!
Woohoo, oh yeah baby
take it off, woo hoo hoo!
Hey Mike, put a
dollar in her bandage
and show the lady a
care, woohoo, all the way
for Crow T.'s bride
groom, woohoo!
Hot sing, hot sing.
- Oh come on, stop the music.
- Look at that action,
look at that neck.
- Hey Crow, Crow,
- What, what?
- Come on, this is wrong.
Think about it, geez.
- Yeah, you know,
you're right Mike,
what was I thinking?
I should be thinking
about my own sweet Servo.
You know why?
I'll tell you why, 'cause
Servo is beautiful.
Servo is so beautiful man.
Servo is like a, like a
precious little flower.
- Right on.
You know what Crow,
your Bachelor party
is the most depressing
thing of my entire life.
- Really?
Well thanks man!
Coming from you
that'd be the last,
honest to God man, I love you.
- Ow, ow, get,
we got movies, we gotta go.
(loud buzzing)
(doors slamming)
- Love you man.
- Not again,
- Hey boss, here's the telegram
that got delivered
to the apartment.
- Now let's see.
- Ah hell I've been traded
to the St. Louis mob.
- A hot tip.
- That's what we need.
- Passenger boy in the
fifth at high aliea.
AH I want no part of it.
Who ever heard of a
fast messenger boy.
Go on, get outta here.
- So discover Cher.
- Hello Americans.
- Our dice are
painstakingly carved
by old world craftsmen.
Sounds like FDR is announcing
the eighth at aquaduct.
- Dice crafters, new
dice in about an hour!
- Well that scene cleared
up a lot of questions.
- I'm enjoying delicious
soups, broths and coffees.
- Boss, did you hear about
the six at high aliea?
- What about it?
- Messenger boy came in first.
- Messenger boy?
What do you know.
- Maybe the guy had something.
- Who?
- The one who sent you
the white?
- God get out of sight.
- Boy that's not hard,
go sit down or...
- It's helps a little.
- Consider that paper
cup my resignation.
- God even the mob
obeys the clean air act.
- Boy when they go outside,
the film really lightens up.
- Now Clara Barton Hooks
hits the waterfront.
- Hello Jackie, where ya going?
- Home of course,
where do you think?
- Just a minute, I
wanna talk to you.
- About new Tide.
- Well make it fast,
I'd like to get home.
- I know something about you.
- You like Tommy in homeroom.
- Do tell, I'd love to hear.
- I hate to say this,
but you haven't been turning
in all the bets you collect.
- You think you know don't you.
- Yes I do.
Six months ago when you first
started to work with us,
you turned in more
bets than you do now.
Well times have changed.
- I'll say they have.
You lived in a cheap hotel room,
now you have a nice apartment.
- I know Schnieder.
- I can add things up.
I'm a bookkeeper, remember?
- You're nothing but a snake.
- Of course I could keep
my mouth shut.
- Or I could go tell
it on the mountains.
- Want a price?
- Yeah.
Half the bets you bucket.
- This thing really
needs panavision.
- You got any money.
- No I don't.
Well let's see, tic
tac and an old kleenex
and there's a picture
of my grandmother.
- Occasion scout had his
hands full didn't he.
- I can let you have $20,
it's all I can spare.
- Maybe you can do
better tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Now don't get sore Jackie.
- Take your hands off me.
- They were off a
while ago actually.
- Why don't you
crawl into the sewer
with the rest of the rats.
- You'll be sorry you said that.
- Although I am gonna
crawl in the sewer
but that's a
complete coincidence.
- Hi boss, I had to find Jan.
- Yeah?
What is it now?
- I got a choice bit
of information for you.
Nothing extra special, but I
though you might be interested.
- It better be good.
Go on.
- Well, you know the girl
Jackie, the girl bookie
that works for us?
- I'm listening.
- I thought you
might like to know
that her hands are like flipey.
- Your lips are like wine.
- You mean she's
holding out on us?
- She buckets better
than half the bets.
- How do you know?
- Well that's easy, I can
show you by the books.
- At first, I'll ready you
the very hungry caterpillar.
- Look here,
when she first started to
work for us six months ago,
she turned in twice the
number of bets she does today.
- I think you got something.
She used to live in
a cheap hotel room.
Now she has a swank apartment.
- I resent that apartment!
- You're all right Monk.
You'll closely watch my
interest and you'll go places.
- Thanks boss.
I always like to be
of help, even if it is
in a small way.
Of course, this shadow work
involves a little expense.
- I know her apartment
move really hurt you.
- You did well Monk.
And--
- Here's 300 J.
- I don't want you to think
that I don't appreciate it.
- Well thanks a lot boss.
- As I said I, always like
to help you run a clean
and upright business.
- Mhm.
- Ah, Joe's getting his
five dollars worth.
- Hey Joe.
- I heard you shot
your woman down.
- Come here.
- Oh she, she crazy
she flipped me over.
- What's up dad?
- Why is it every
time I watch you,
you're in the gym
with one of the girls?
- Because it's an
easier place to find me.
- Come in my office,
I wanna talk to you.
- Okay.
- Joe paved the way
for Herbe Villages.
- She used to live
in a cheap hotel,
now she lives in
a swank apartment.
I can't get over that!
- Cards clean and
pressed while you wait.
- I want you to
go to the stables.
- My pet rock.
- What again?
But boss that will make
it three times this week.
- You should complain, you're
eating regularly aren't ya?
- You but it's--
- Do tell.
- Maybe for seven
or eight years.
- Maybe you'll be lucky
and get a shady cell.
- Ah, I'm gon'
quit this business.
- Well I could always put
you back selling peanuts
at the arena.
- Oh no, not that,
anything but that!
- It was probably a very
good peanut seller though.
- All right, what's
name of the horse.
- Puncture proof,
you know what to do.
- Puncture him.
- Okay.
I know my stuff.
- I gey my partner Rusty.
Hey Rusty!
- Get new Italian sidekick.
- Hey boss, there's a
heavy play on Golden Boy
in the fourth of pilico.
We've got over five G's on him,
should we lay some of it off.
- Sure, who are you?
- Take a chance on two G's.
Spread the other three
on Mow and Hiney.
- Okay boss.
- Oh say, did you
get hold of Told Ya.
- I sure did boss,
she's outside now.
- Nice, ew.
To you.
- What does Scalli want me for?
- I don't know, he
wouldn't say a word to me.
- You wouldn't--
- Partners aren't we?
- Oh kiss an itch.
- The boss wants to see
you now, in his office.
- Would you take off the
rubber nose and glasses please?
- So you got an filing
you need done or not or...
- You may think you're smart,
but you can't outsmart
an old timer like me.
- You don't know what
you're talking about.
- That you're bucketing most
of the bets you collect.
You're nothing but
a cheap chizzler.
- You can't talk to me that day.
- You needn't deny anything.
Monk has clearly
shown me every detail.
- Monk.
- That surprises you?
- You mean you believe him?
- Yeah.
- He's nothing but a sewer rat.
You forget, Monk
is working for me
and has been for a long time.
He's been checking on you
and shadowing you for
the past few weeks.
- I may be a sucker
but I, you and Monk
are made of the same filth.
- Hey.
- Especially for you
to get out of town
or get all facts.
- Save her Peaches!
- If I catch you
hanging around again,
I'll have you beaten
up, now get out of here.
- Well actually he's a
pretty lenient mobster.
- As they go.
(chickens clucking)
- Ah, the fertile
breeding stables
of Pelomed chicken farms.
- With champion stud chicken
Manowar.
- Wow, that's a
really big sports car.
(robots giggling)
- Did you have location
scouting ever come up?
- Why doesn't he
just walk backwards?
- You know it's the music
that makes this
scene come to life.
- Morning sir, welcome
to Diamond Star Ranch.
- Well.
(horse neighing)
- Whoa Joe, you've returned!
- And I, I know it's not much
but I got you this ring.
- Anyone see a
horse around here?
(horse neighing)
Ooh, professor Firefly!
- I'm sorry I thought
you were coming on to me,
I'm sorry I misread the singles.
- All right, give me some.
- Woohoo, woohoo!
- Yum yum yum yum yum.
- Cafeteria ladies
on their off hours.
Here at futon galleries we're
having the best sale ever.
Wrestling for the ladies
and hot dogs for the kids.
A Bob Hope entourage prepares
for another USO tour.
Pantyliner has wings!
- If Russ Myers had direction
Clare Booth loses the women.
- I don't feel fresh today.
- I'll show you fresh.
- This is all for the
first ladies medal
in physical fitness.
- If you thought Eunice
Kennedy Schriver wasn't sexy,
mmm, wow.
- Hey the movie's back on track!
- What are you thinking about?
- Playdoh.
- Oh just thinking Mr. Scalli
is such a wonderful gentleman.
- Hmm, I could tell
you a thing or two
about your Mr. Scalli.
- You don't seem to like him.
- I'm so dumb.
- Well, let me tell
you what happened
when my best friend
applied to him for a job.
- Come in.
- That's right,
just keep coming in,
you've got it, yes.
- Mr Scalli, I'm afraid
I don't have the money
I promised you today.
But if you'd only give
me a little more time.
- Listen I'd get
all upset Beverly,
I'll give you all
the time you need.
- Time's up!
- You have a job?
- Well I had one, but I'm
gonna get another one soon.
- Did you get fired.
- Yes,
they said I was drunk.
- I was so high I
wouldn't have known!
- That's funny isn't it?
- Go on girl.
- I wish I could get
drunk instead of--
- These pills you're taking
are quite expensive Beverly.
An expense I'm afraid I can't
handle myself at the moment.
- I need my Tagamats!
- Please don't cut me off
Mr. Scalli, please.
- I'm Bonnie Bedelia.
- I'll get another job
soon, I've been promised.
- What Beverly, a job?
Doing what?
You're in no shape
to work right now.
Are you still living at home?
Maybe your folks could--
- Home,
I haven't got a home, and I
haven't gotten any folks either.
Would you call a drunken
father and mother folks?
- Sure.
- I don't.
No Mr. Scalli, I'm on my own.
I can't remember
when I haven't been.
- Wait a minute,
there just may be a
way to help you out?
- Do you think so Mr. Scalli?
I'd do anything to
pay you what I owe.
I'll take any kind of
a job, washing dishes,
doing laundry, anything.
- Well that isn't exactly
what I had in mind
but you might be able
to do my a favor.
- My basement needs drywall.
- A favor?
- Yes, a certain friend of
mine, Mr. Gomez has a place
not far from here.
- I want you to rough him up.
- A little cabaret you
know, dining, dancing,
a little drinking,
that sort of thing.
- I'd make a very
good waitress now.
- Well, not exactly what
I had in mind my dear.
- You see Mr. Gomez
is a business man.
He caters to a very
fine class of people.
- Uh oh.
- Of course,
some of his customers
drop in without a date.
- Oh boy.
- And come girls
act as hostesses to make
them feel more at home.
- Oh I see.
Well, just how much at
home do they have to feel?
- Well said my dear.
You understand,
keep them company,
have a few drinks and then...
- Oh no Scalli, I
couldn't do that.
I couldn't be a--
- An actress!
- I've sunk pretty
low but doing that,
- To the Vedder Amway!
- Oh no!
- Oh come now Beverly you're
much too pretty a girl to cry,
it's really not that bad.
It would give you a chance
to get back on your feet,
a little money to buy, well,
whatever you might want,
understand?
Whatever you need.
- Yes.
- Ew boogers.
- I understand Mr. Scalli.
I understand.
I don't suppose there's
any reason why I shouldn't,
is there?
- That's the spirit we
need in our hookers!
- I have no bad attitude do I?
Just myself, isn't that right?
I can do anything I please.
- Maybe I'll protract this
scene a little longer.
- It will be nice to
have a little money again
to buy whatever I like.
- Toast.
- Yes it would be nice.
- There's some heroin
I've had my eye on.
- All right Mr. Scalli,
I'll see your Mr. Gomez.
- And I'll raise you a Gonzalez.
- Maybe I'll... get a chance
to forget a lot of things.
- All this for a car loan.
- Maybe after I get a
little money I could go away
and maybe start over again.
- I don't see that happening.
- Ill see him Mr. Scalli,
what's the address?
- Oh, it's my turn to act, oh,
seven, one, six, pimp circle.
- Did he really do that?
- He's just playing
no good if you ask me.
He's a sort of a guy who would
change a girls evening stroll
from a recreation
to an occupation.
- Ooh, Miss Metaphor.
- But he wants me
to be his girl.
- I am a girl aren't I?
- His girl is a lot of girls.
And you happen to
be only one of them.
- I don't understand,
he treats me so nice.
- Listen kid, a lustful
look to that guy
is like a bugle call
to a cavalry mount.
- But he said he'd help me.
And I want to be a champ
like Clare Mortensen.
- Idiot.
- I know you mean well kid,
I used to believe his lies
and sometimes I still do.
But take my advice,
- Wear socks.
- I never saw any good come
out of him, and I never will.
- Miss Manners in Personal Best.
- Say boss, you know that
horse called Puncture Proof?
- What about him?
- He dropped dead this
afternoon at the starting gate.
- Well.
- You're right I
had that coming.
- Quick Joe, think of
something cute and ethnic!
- Just what did you do out
there at the track anyway?
- Just what you told me boss.
- I didn't tell you
to kill a horse.
- Maybe the horse was
weak, how should I know?
Or maybe it had the
flu or something?
- You're trying to be funny?
- Listen boss,
I'll make it up to you.
(speaking foreign language)
- No you don't, go
on, get outta here
'till I send for ya.
- The one minute mafia.
- His mustache is like little
windshield wipers, cute.
- It's about time you go
over and call on Scalli.
There has been too much silence.
- How's Monk doing?
- Monk's been doing a fine
job of checking for me,
but I want you to drop
in and refresh his memory
after that $35 grand he owes me.
- Ill make it a point
to drop in on him today.
- Boy the Mr. Big scenes
really rescue the movie.
- Oh you bet.
- Whoa, Peaches and Herb.
- Oh it still fits fine!
- I'd rather see Bob
Hoskins in that sweater.
- Am I intruding?
- No protruding.
- Oh, come right in.
- Sorry, Peaches is
getting kinda clingy.
- And she's a beautiful
and a wonderful, ah!
- That's all right, I guess
I'm old enough to take a hint.
It doesn't seem so long ago
that I too believed your lies
but I guess it won't be long
until I'm not even
wanted around here.
- You know she doesn't
mean anything to me.
- Sure, I can believe that.
It's the very same lie
you give her about me.
- It's always awkward
when you have to break
up with your grandma.
- What am I gonna
do with you anyway?
- Dove tears.
- Oh, take your hands off me.
- This is Orlan!
- I can still remember
your lies about all
the wonderful things
you were gonna do for me.
Sure, look at me now.
Picking up towels in
a gym locker room.
- I tell ya, with me
it's strictly business.
- Sure I can see that.
You and her, some business.
- To shame a mob guy.
- I'm sorry boss.
- I killed that horse again.
- I, I didn't mean
to break up any conference.
- By coming in here,
you did my a favor.
Oh say, don't forget
tonight we're gonna see
the leopard woman wrestle
the panther woman, same seat.
Don't forget.
- I won't boss.
- Yeah same seats so we don't
have to shoot anymore footage.
- Now Calvin Coolage refereed.
- Oh it's Sean Young
after another part.
- Mmmm let me get
unbunched here, there.
- The embarrassing thing
is she had to ride the bus
to get here.
(bell dinging)
- Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the feature
bout of the evening.
- Hubba hubba.
- In this corner,
weighing 108 pounds,
the leopard lady.
- Alf Landin ladies
beat all men.
- And at 110 pounds, the
famous panther woman.
- Oui, I am that person.
- Crowd's enthusiasm
is quickly dimmed.
- Okay ladies, no spraying.
- Their hands are
so nice and smooth,
you can't tell which
one is the mother!
- All right we're
gonna meet back here
and go to Chili's right?
You can drive?
No I can drive, I can drive,
it will be okay, okay.
- All right the victor
will drag half of the loser
back to her front porch
and present it to her owner.
(bell dinging)
- What's new pussycat,
whoa wow wow wow wow.
Okay you can borrow my eyeliner.
You have to wonder what the
rejected footage looked like.
- What rejected footage?
Oh I should have
anticipated that.
- Oh we're seeing him so happy.
- You know I like
the idea of two women
dressed like cats and
fighting but I don't know,
the execution or something.
- Well perhaps women
dressed like a peckerie
and the other dressed
like parrot playing Majan.
- Ah, that's got something.
- Spit it out.
- Cathy and Moe split up.
Cut off from the
National Treasury,
Princess Ann and
Princess Margaret
are forced to earn their keep.
- Ooh.
(funky '80s music)
- Women on the verge of
a three point takedown.
I'll snap your bra, I will!
- Well the wrestling match
has an infinite variety
of moves, huh?
- Oh wait, this isn't
working, here try this,
oh sorry, sorry here wait,
how many of God's laws
does this violate?
- It's like a very
awkward pickpocketing.
- Everything okay here ladies,
anything I can do to
help or not, or...
- Uncle, uncle!
I said uncle about a
million times Vicky God,
don't you listen to me?
- I don't like the new
models ink plotline.
- Ah!
Ah!
- Whee, ow!
- Womanex!
(robots making beat)
- Someone left their
lasagna in the corner.
Hey, it's that women
right over there
who's making all the noise!
- Ma'am we'll have to
ask you to settle down.
Ah!
- Strictly ballroom two.
- Uh Rene, I can see
your underpants, Vick,
- Yes, I want Joe Fraser!
- The trumming Zoe Calbo
ladies and gentlemen,
Zoe Calbo.
- Thank you thank you.
- Well, that's our shift, see
you tomorrow at seven then.
- Hi, we're here for
the file clerk position.
- Here again?
- We're on tomorrow.
- Yeah, Mr. Big just
asked me to drop in
to give you his regards.
- Well how nice.
- He's real interested in you.
- Little old me?
- Quit kiddin'.
- He must know when
he means business.
He wants that money, his
patience is running out.
- Ah, remind me to
murder you later.
- Swell looking bunch of
things you got out there.
Even Mr. Big says it's a
smart cover up you got.
Plenty of clean sports like
lady wrestling front for you.
- Why don't you dry up?
- Well see what Lucy
and Ethel are up to.
- A glance says so
much with those two.
- What is that, play
school's my first desk?
- Just walked off
the set there, sorry.
- Are you Umberto Scalli?
- That's what
everybody calls me.
- Well then this is
for you Mr. Scalli.
- Thanks Bob.
- Bob, Bob.
- Don't get excited, the
same way the girls did,
through the front entrance.
- Ha ha, Joe...
- What is it boss?
- It's a coupon
for a happy meal.
- It's a subpoena
to appear before
the crime investigating
committee.
- Oh for fun!
- That's nice.
- He wouldn't do any
singing would you?
- I do a talking blues
that's pretty good.
- I could of course.
But I don't think will.
That is if Mr. Big will
cooperate let us say
in this little
matter between us?
- You've got a point there,
I'll speak to him about it.
But remember, Mr. Big's
first love is money.
- I thought his first
love was the theater.
- Now boss, I don't
wanna get mixed up
in this investigating business.
Now remember I
don't speak English.
- Oh no, that's the senate!
We will now break from our
regularly scheduled wrestling
to bring you, wrestling.
- These are just the
compulsories so...
- I'd rather see gold
in my ear in that getup.
- Peaches is definitely
champion material.
- I want to shout
words of encouragement.
- Ah,
that move, that established
Peaches reputation
as an innovator.
- It's like a stag film produced
by the League of Women voters.
- Trent Williams!
- This film awakened Eleanor
Roosevelt's sexuality.
- Ah, the cleavage monitor!
- Someone's learning
typing in the next room.
- I wanna join them so badly!
- Hey Ralphie Boy!
- She looks like a
leatherback turtle.
- One thing that
really comes through
is the filmmakers
love for the subject.
- Yes, give generously to
the US Olympic committee.
- Tastes great, must
feel like stuffing,
- Potatoes.
- Lincoln.
- Douglas!
I think maybe a second draft
might have helped this movie.
- Yes, the forbidden secret
backroom of your aunt's house.
- Uh girls I have to take
the mat in for cleaning.
If I could just, oh...
- Well she could have
worn clothes for this,
it wouldn't have hurt the scene.
(loud slapping)
- Oh man, crotch slapping.
That's below the belt!
- She's got a frontal bike rack!
She looks like a ramulen!
- She has a little bit
of Yogi Berra in her too.
Ride along with me,
under the sea--
- By being turned on
by a woman who is long dead.
(robots shuddering)
(robots laughing)
Ah cripes,
we haven't sold
a single car yet.
- Say Munch, pick up my tickets
for tonight's wrestling bout?
- Sure, same year round.
- Same seats, same gestures.
- Great match tonight.
Champion Clara Mortenson
versus Rita Martinez.
- We read the credits, you know.
- Oh so you wanna bet?
- Quit kidding,
bookkeepers aren't
supposed to bet.
- Just checking.
- I've been listening
to that same gay
from you ever since
I worked for you.
- Scalli's way around
the office is legendary.
- Mosey on down to the war
room and see what's happening.
- I want you to
understand that is to be
a very private conversation.
- Pat Nixon!
- Anything we say will not
go beyond these four walls.
- Joe needs a tutor.
- I understand.
- I was wondering if
you'd be interested
in a little piece of business,
strictly business
you understand.
- Wrestling me.
- That depends
on the business.
- Well,
I'll be frank with you.
- I have no bladder control.
- How'd you like to throw
your bout with Rita Martinez?
- I could make it
very interesting.
Say, $1,000
- Throw a wrestling match?
No.
- No.
- I'm surprised to
hear you talk that way.
I really don't know
how to take it.
- As I say it's business.
- It's fun sometimes.
- I'm sorry Mr. Scalli,
I'm not interested.
Wrestling is one of the
few remaining clean sports.
- That and cockfighting.
- We who make our living at it
intend to keep it that way.
I'm not interested in
that kind of money.
Not even for one,
two, five or $10,000.
- Well I didn't
mean to offend you.
- It's scum like you that
not only ruin the sport
but the athletes
in public as well.
Good day.
- How about prostitution, drugs?
You can get back to me.
- I've been looking for you.
- What is it Clare?
- Get your things
out of your locker.
You're leaving
Scalli's gym at once.
This place is a hotbox!
- What about my contract?
- I know what I'll
tell Mr. Scalli with it
and I'm gonna do all I can
to run him out of
this profession.
- You don't seen to like Scout.
I hope he dies with a
fishbone in his throat.
Come on, let's go.
- You know Peaches has a
fresh natural stupidness
that isn't forced
or contrived or...
- I don't want you
to be offended,
'cause I say it's
strictly business.
- You think because I'm Mexican,
you can take advantage of me
but I am no fool.
- Zelda!
- I thought you'd understand.
- You forget that I am the
champion of all Mexico.
- 'Cause I am Mexican!
- In this sport it takes
hard work to get there
and guts to stay there.
- Well you're right
but after all.
- Goodbye Mr. Scalli.
- Scalli sadly misread
the motivations
of his women wrestlers.
Tonight at the Corn Palace,
five time winner, Sawyer Brown.
- Uh regular or unleaded ma'am.
- Congratulations Clara
and Rita on your wedding.
(doors shutting)
(futuristic beeping)
(soft guitar playing)
♪ There is love ♪
- I love you guys.
♪ Lemon dream very pretty. ♪
- Thank you, thank you.
Now we are gathered here today
to get through this
thing called life.
Electric word life
it means forever
and that might, excuse
me wrong speech,
ah here we are, yes, marriage.
The coming together
of two to make one.
Two people, two separate
perfectly happy people
who haven't been held
down by life until now
but no, some lame
brain gets in his head
that he can't make it alone.
I'm too weak, I
need a hand to hold!
Suddenly the idiot gets married
and all hell breaks loose
but we're in love, ah!
- Sir do you think
maybe we should.
Oh think maybe this.
(punches walloping)
(Dr. F groaning)
- You broke the broke--
- Wrestling!
Oh you, oh, oh oh.
Oh, oh--
- Oh blow my head,
oh no oh no,
- Hey you let go of...
(men grunnting)
No, no I got shoulder out no,
you didn't send me
you'll never pass.
No, get off, ah maybe I'm
not ready for marriage.
(funky '80s music)
- Hope we're done with that.
- Geez I just got out of bed
and now I have to wrestle.
- In this corner
in the house coat,
- Gentlemen, this is the
main event of the evening.
Introducing at 134 pounds.
- 132.
- The champion of
Mexico, Rita Martinez.
- Go home everybody, go home.
- And weighting 130 pounds.
- I'm so fat.
- World champion, Clara--
- Peller!
- Mortenson.
- Also know as the
tough, old broad.
- I thought we were
meeting at Chee Chee's,
- No I thought we said Chili's.
Are you mad?
- You're mad.
- Oh no it's just
that I thought--
- Let's talk about it tonight
att Antigo, I'll drive.
- Okay, fair enough.
- Okay.
- Now, have you been biting
your cuticles gain Sherry,
what about you?
- This is gonna be so great,
this is what it's all about.
Yes yes yes, ah!
- Ah, it's Iggy Pop!
- Jesus, she's too mannish
for Alice B. Tokeless.
- You know it really is a shame
so few girls thought this
was opinion back then.
- Ladies and gentlemen I
cannot condone women wrestling.
I would be provericating if
I said it was a valid sport.
- Hold still we'll get
out of here sooner.
- So everyday I just
can't find your earring!
- Can't we just throw
a dropcloth over them?
(robot making stuttering sounds)
- Uh, uh pardon, me,
you shouldn't do that.
All I can say is that
it must have been
much easier to get
turned on back then.
- No Lupita,
- Oh the bad spot,
the bad spot, ow!
- Your thigh is not the
best smelling you know.
- Boy if ever a movie
needed El Santo.
- This is so wrong.
- This movie has taken the joy
out of looking at
someone's hinder.
- My loins will
never stir again.
- You don't have loins.
- You know maybe
this is titillating
to some of the lower animals.
- So just otters or Vikings?
- Wrestling is very glamorous.
(Crow aggressively humming)
You know Clara Mortenson does
so much more than wrestle,
she does so much
for the community.
- When women try to figure
out the lunch tab, thank you!
- Just think if this match
were on interactive video,
we'd be able to smell it too!
Gilda Radner and Carol
Leafer in a grudge match.
Ah, got it, ah Rite honey, you
got a big pimple back here,
want me to pop it for ya?
- Take it easy Clara,
I'm supposed to be in
a wedding tomorrow!
(woman screaming)
- My hair extensions!
- Not many professional
sports people
just flat out scream
during a match.
Yes wrestling, a clean sport.
- Raw Lakosta, out loud.
- Can I get some
help here please?
♪ Lady wrestlers, my
love is wild and ♪
♪ Lee Ross, lady love ♪
- It would appear to me
that they are wrestling
hence this match is
in stark contrast
to the previous matches.
- Ref I call, she's not Mexican.
I hate it when my mom dressed
up like that to do yard work.
(woman screaming)
- Ah yes that's it, let
it out Rita that's right.
Wrestling is
frustrating isn't it.
- Okay, come here, come here,
what were you screaming
about earlier?
Ah!
- Ah, oh.
- Stop it.
- That's called the
croppy isn't it.
- She's got the best leg
flop thing in the business.
- Ah, ah.
- Ah.
This is the pilot for
the better sex videos.
- Ah.
Tony Orlando and Don in their
most provocative show ever.
- Ah.
- Ah!
- Oh lava, just
about all of this leg
could possibly stand
and I don't think I
could see anymore.
- Ah!
- Sorry I turned into
the devil for a sec.
- Maybe this movie
has deep meaning
in some whorey
dreamworld somewhere.
- Oh Rita, your deoderant has
turned all white and flakey,
oh flep!
- Ah when you wrestle
Clara Mortenson,
you're gonna get whisker burns.
- I had to do this in
theater class once.
- On purpose?
- I don't think Rita has any
idea how do to the Heimlach.
- Ah.
- Ah!
(Tom shrieking)
The Beatles!
- Ah!
- Ah, no points for that,
it's just plain fun.
- There can be only one!
- I guess if you were a
gay guy who liked truckers
you might find these
women attractive.
- You know there's
thousands of Clara's army
who show up for every match?
- Yeah they camp out
at Tickettron outlets
to get tickets to each match.
- Ah another sellout crowd.
(robots making
dramatic sound effects)
This could be a setback
for pasty white skin.
(Tom imitating a donkey)
- I think Clara's overdependent
on the floppy thing.
- This is really expanding
my notion of womanhood.
I think that ref likes me,
he keeps looking at me!
- Do you know George
Well reveres this sport?
- Good.
This is where Forrest
Gump shows up.
Rita this has been
fun, we gotta get ready
for Stacey's lingerie party.
- Ah Harry Dean Stanton.
- Is this the induction
film when you go to hell?
- I think it might be.
- You know frankly I wasn't
prepared for so much wrestling,
I thought there'd be
more racketeering.
(Tom fake puking)
- Oh stop it I get airsick!
- Oh boy that is--
- Oh that is sure awesome,
I love that stuff.
- Sure love it.
This bug you huh,
this bug you huh?
This bug you at
all, this bug you?
- Early Charlie Horse research.
- Ah hah, ah, the leg is
on the other thigh now.
- I think they're
gonna wrap it up,
they don't wanna miss
Regis and Kathy Lee.
- Ooh.
- Ah, ah.
- Ah!
- Max Lonsito!
- Whoa I'd like
to get in on that!
Wow, yeah.
- Rita please,
I'm still in my
child bearing years.
- So 6:30 and Sin
Tito's right, right?
Okay.
- Andy did you hear about Elvis?
- Oh that'll induce labor.
Oh wait, are they
using stuntman now?
- Ah.
- Ah, ah!
- Uh pardon me, did
you drop your wrestler?
- This is like an
infomercial for Doan's pills.
- I think the editor
went on a lunch break.
- Ah.
- Ah!
- It's like a tilt-a-whirl.
- Ah oh oh Clara your
hand is freezing.
- I don't think I much like
the new start search category.
- I don't think I
could ever date a woman
who could bench press me.
- Oh come here my sweet
little baby, look at her!
- That's for making the
scene go on so long!
Ah she's got kind of a
Purnell Roberts strut.
- She could take Purnell.
- Oh yeah.
- We're still on
for Santigo's right?
Huh?
- Okay I've got it.
- They want us to do
the scene over again.
- Honey said Scalli's to take
the stand in a few minutes.
- Just one wrong
word from Scalli
and he won't live
to say another one.
- I know a quick drying
cement we can pack him in.
- Did I ask you anything?
- But Chief I just wanna help!
- I'll call for you
when I need you.
Now set up all of you
so I can hear the
investigation over the radio.
- Ah the combination
wall safe and radio.
- [Man On Radio] First off I
would remind you Mr. Scalli
that you're under oath.
- Gold and silver shine!
- [Man On Radio] Perjery.
(funky '80s music)
- Now--
- Does this clip
need any set-up?
- What is your business?
- And I'll look at you
and my doppleganger.
- I'm a promoter
of women wrestlers.
- You make a lot of money
at that business don't you?
- This director is
outwooded Ed Wood.
- I have my income
tax records to show.
- You're not answering
the question.
You do make a lot of money
in that business don't you!
- Uh it keeps me in weird ties.
- Depends on what
you mean by a lot.
- Is the women's
wrestling business
your only source of
income Mr. Scalli?
- Uh I'm a nude model
for art students too.
- Yes.
Woman wrestling business is
my only source of income.
- Geez how long
has this been here?
- It's a clean sport.
- Lucky bastard.
- [Umberto] That's why
they go make money on it.
- How about horse
racing Mr. Scalli.
- Oh he's really got
his teeth into him.
- It's out of my line.
- You mean to tell
this committee
that you never bet
on horse races?
- I'm a wrestling promoter,
I'm not interested in horses.
- Do you know any
bookmakers Mr. Scalli?
- Well, Simon and
Schuster, Hoden Miffilin.
- I know a lot of people.
I don't ask a man his business.
- I wonder what country
this is taking place in?
- Seven years ago you
were arrested in New York
for making book.
- Ah those were our solid days.
- Do you deny that Mr. Scalli.
- There's a frame up, I've
never made a book in my life.
- Yes you have.
And before this committee
is through with you,
we're going to prove it!
- You haven't anything on me.
- That's what you'd like
to think isn't it Scalli.
- We'll be right back
with our next guest,
- After we're through
with this investigation,
we're going to
know all about you.
- Your turn ons
and your turn offs.
- And about a man who
is known as Mr. Big.
- My parking meter!
- They just lost their audience.
- That'll be all
for the present,
we'll send for you again soon.
- And you'll be appearing at
the Westwood Hoe next weekend,
is that right?
Well thanks again Scalli buh
bye, we'll be right back.
No I don't see any nose hairs.
- You here again?
Come here.
(group snickering)
- Joe was the Brian
Benben of his day.
- Oh I can never have any fun.
- Come on I wanna
talk to you again.
- All right.
- About this phony
Italian accent of yours.
- Say Chief, Monk's here.
- Bring him in.
- All right stand in the
place where you live.
- What is it Monk?
- Things look pretty
suspicious Chief.
Scalli sent me down to
the bank twice today
and I've drawn out
large sums of money.
- Yeah.
- He's got it all
in the office safe.
- Go on, go on, what else?
- Well he asked me three times
what I was doing tonight.
It looks as if he
doesn't want me
or anyone else in the place.
- You mean there's no
one at the gym tonight?
- I'm pretty sure.
- That isn't enough,
call up and check.
- Would you please clean
your nails elsewhere?
- I gotta call and get
my bank balance first.
I better check on
mother as well.
- Strut pout put it out, that's
what you want from grandma!
(phone ringing)
- Hello.
- Hello Ruby this is Monk.
- What do you want?
- Any of the boys around?
- No everyone's gone home but me
and I'm leaving in
about five minutes.
- That was Ruby, she's
leaving in five minutes,
there isn't a soul in the place.
- How do we get in?
- Let me go ahead, I'll
open the back door for you,
I'll even await
until you arrive.
- All right boys, give
Monk a 20 minute start
and go to Sculley's office
and hijack that safe.
I want my $35 grand
and I want it now.
- It's a valuable tip.
- Did you also
hear about the Dane
that used to live
in a cheap hotel.
Now she's got a swank apart--
- Will you knock it off?
There, go buy yourself
something pretty.
- Why, thanks Chief.
- Mr. Big is a chilling
presence in this film.
- See, I knew it
was in effeisions.
- What are you doing here
this hour of the night,
expecting someone?
- No boss, I was just leaving.
- Well get out of here.
- Oh someone's a bitch
and it's not me
and it's not Joe.
- He's gotta erase
the chalkboard
so don't be suspicious.
(intense music)
- Music, why here, why now?
Why us!
- Okay people we've
completely lost the lights,
let's roll film.
- Well at least we didn't
have to see these guys
wrestle in little outfits, huh?
- Well, then again.
- Sorry, I mean like I told you.
- Yes boss.
- I parked it in a clear spot
just so that we can
get out in a hurry.
- Plat, this is my
super cool fort,
just make sure my
sister doesn't see us.
- Well let's hurry
up a little faster.
- Oh no the second
act is starting!
- Somebody just came
in, they must have take
the back door unlocked!
- They should make
deposits more often.
- Get out of here in a hurry.
- All right give it to me.
- Maybe a class
in small business
administration would help.
(intense music)
- All right hold up guys,
we have to let the other
caper play through.
- Boss not to pay you cash,
what about the
donuts for the staff?
- I close it.
(intense music)
- No.
- Oh.
- Today the sidekick
community mourned the loss
of one of it's greats.
(gunshot firing)
- Oh he's Hindu!
- Give me sport
coat to Al Pacino.
- This is Quentin Tarantino's
most shocking film.
- The mob squad.
- It's the contract
parking gang.
- Have you been noticing
many odd occurrences lately.
Oh it's true.
- Hey tin machine.
- Yeah.
- You know, I never
thought I'd be sorry
to see them lose the
whole wrestling angle.
- Quick, let's follow, let's
start out high speed chase.
- There we go.
- If we, yeah, you there?
Okay there we go.
- Zoom.
And at night, the town
of Menaqua comes alive
with entertainment,
recreation and great food.
They shouldn't have
let Eric Rommer
direct a high speed
chase sequence.
- Ooh, I'm dying, still
I better watch my driver.
Oh.
(gunshot firing)
- I'm dying in a rush.
(gunshots firing)
- Ha ha, must be the
same magic bullet
that got Connolly.
- Packed with cops, this
movie really satisfies.
- Ooh, you should
never bit a hangnail.
(gunshot firing)
- Police cars not
dissimilar to these
were called to the scene.
(robots mimicking music)
(intense music)
- This is the narrative
approximation of something
that may or may
not have happened.
- Why is there a French
Horn on top of his car?
It's neat how one senate
hearing can wipe out
all of organized crime.
- Look it's Herbie the cop car!
Sounds like the Ukrainian
national anthem.
(robots humming)
- Ukraine, yeah, Ukraine, yeah,
oh hey you, Ukrainia,
my bitter homeland.
Your straight minds,
your big reactors,
so the message is
tampering with rest
from delivering punishments
swift and short.
- This movie needs another
big bowl of fresh Peaches.
Where we are is anybody's guess.
- I think these shots are
rejected from Monster A-go-go.
(robots mimicking music)
(intense music)
- Ironically, well
actually there is no irony.
- What's that, do you
recognize that sound?
- Sir have you seen anyone
who may have tampered
with ladies wrestling?
- Told ya we shouldn't
have teepeed that house.
Oh you call that a mustache?
- Maybe they're here
at the imagitoriam sir.
- Ukraine, yeah.
- Quick, through the wardrobe.
Oh no, that's us in the corner,
that's us in the spotlight!
- Ukraine, yeah,
my sweet Ukraine yeah.
- Ah hell with is,
let's just shoot.
(gunshots firing)
This is the sequence
John Woo directed.
Ah poopy.
- Where's Mr. Big when
they need him, huh?
- Well they'll all be
sentenced to 20 years
of looking at Clara Mortenson.
- And once again
the world is saved
from ladies wresting.
- Ah, what a powerful ending.
This movie was the
"Jaws" of its day.
People were afraid to
go to ladies wrestling.
- Ukraine yeah!
My home yeah!
- Ukraine, yeah!
(doors slamming shut)
- Boy oh boy,
there sure was a lot of
wrestling in this movie,
hey professor Hurts?
- Seemed like a lot of wrestling
to me Count Deala Pain,
maybe too much wrestling.
Do you agree sir Slams-a lot?
- Oh definitely Professor
Hurts, too much wrestling.
Heck even too much slamming
and I'm sir Slams-a lot!
- Yeah you know what I feel
the same way about the pain
and I'm Count Deala Pain.
- Oh well, gotta let
it air Mr. Deala Pain.
- Oh yeah, yes I do.
I have a letter, it's
Count Deala Pain.
- Sorry.
- Did you say that?
All right, here we go,
this one is from
Preston Enright.
- Ooh.
Betcha I could
slam Preston a lot.
- Take it easy, Preston
Enright sends in a lecture here
from Noam Chomsky fellow.
- Hey Count Deala Pain,
my name is Professor
Hurts and Professor Hurts
is not into lectures!
How about you Slams?
- I'm not a bright guy,
pretty much born to slam!
- All right fine, I
got another letter here
from David Sharer, age five.
- Perfect!
- And he says, why
don't you put that
on still story there Cambot?
- Oh nice drawing!
- Very nice.
- Isn't that great?
He says I laugh
during movie time.
- [Crow] Well that speaks
volumes doesn't it.
- Look at that picture there.
David Sherer, for all
your insurance needs.
- Three locations.
- Well I guess that's
about it Dr. F.
- Hey Forester, hey
buddy, less wrestling
and the pain and
slamming next time, okay?
- Yeah!
Yeah,
oh he doesn't even care.
Come on, ready?
- Gotta slam him down.
- Shoulder to elbow hook up.
- Come on!
- Wrestle.
- Well Mike,
we finally got security
all beefed up down here,
even got rid of that
weird-ass family.
So I don't think
you'll be seeing any
breaches of security
anytime soon.
♪ Everybody could say it now ♪
- Frank!
We'll just thank you,
listen, a little bit over.
Frank we gotta do something,
we can't even keep
Lisa Lobe outta here!
- Oh but Clay, I really
go for that thoughtful,
sensitive cigarette smoking,
intelligent, artistic
type of coffee shop girl.
- Frank I got reason to
believe that you're Lisa
dating Ethan Hawke.
- Trip!
Horrid!
She's a man, be gone with you!
Be gone!
(somber outro music)
- It's gone.
- Where'd it go?